A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, China Medical Board records, RG 4 FA114
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller Foundation records, China Medical Board records, RG 4
1913-1929
Rockefeller Archive Center
China Medical Board. Beijing (China)
China Medical Board (U.S)
Rockefeller Foundation
FA114
40 Cubic Feet 96 document cases
Arrangement
Series I, Appropriations, is divided into two subseries. Subseries I runs from 1913-1918, and is in a numerical filing system. Each person, organization or topic has been given a number. In general the administrative topics run for the first 50 numbers. Numbers 50-83 are the missionary societies. From #84 on come the individual mission hospitals. They are filed according to province. Anhui runs from 84-88, Chekiang from 89-100 and so on.
Subseries II covers the years 1919-1929. It is an alphabetical series in which administrative and general topics are mixed in with appropriations.
Numerous cross references exist in most of the files. They indicate a reference for the year only, rather than for a specific date. A card index (1914-1927) of correspondence is available for individuals and organizations.
When consulting a folder on a particular missionary society or hospital, it is wise to also check the other society folders of society hospitals for additional material.
Series II is the Financial Series.
Series III contains minutes and annual reports.
Related Materials
Records and series which appear to be missing are presumably with the China Medical Board, Incorporated, and their files should be consulted. The files of the China Medical Board, Inc., are on deposit at the Rockefeller Archive Center.
Scope and Contents
Important subjects nclude: missions and missionary societies, Chinese political situation, World War I, economy, exchange, Boxer indemnity, Chinese education-secondary, premedical and medical, public health, epidemics, famine, floods, union universities, dentistry, nursing, pharmacy, agriculture, trade schools, student unrest, labor problems, anti-Christian and antiforeign feeling, opium, Japanese earthquake, x-ray, real estate, vivisection, textbook translation, Sino-Japanese relations.
Among the correspondents are: Paul Monroe, Alan Gregg, Alfred S. K. Sze, W. W. Peter, George Heber Jones, Starr Murphy, John R. Mott, Francis W. Peabody, Wickliffe Rose, Frederick T. Gates, Harry Pratt Judson, John D. Rockefeller Jr., Robert E. Speer, Henry S. Houghton, Roger S. Greene, Wallace Buttrick, Amos P. Wilder, Edward H. Hume, Simon Flexner, Walter H. Page, Cecil Davenport, Franklin C. McLean, N. Gist Gee, Paul Reinsch, Chang Poling, Wellington Koo, Sidney Gulick, L. C. Goodrich, Ernest D. Burton, William W. Cadbury, John B. Grant, William Welch, Barry Smith, Hans Zissner, G. E. DeSchweinitz, Frank Mason North, Arthur T. Brown, Stanley White, John W. Wood, Stephen Corey, William E. Strong, James L. Barton, F. H. Hawkins, Thomas Cochrane, T. B. Ray, D. Duncan Main, A. M. Dunlap, Archibald P. Chien, W. S. Carter, Lucy W. Peabody, Anson Phelps Stokes, Palmer Bevis, H. C. Mao.
The Foundation's archives include:
Projects General Correspondence Administration, Program and Policy China Medical Board International Health Board/Division Field Offices Treasurer's Office Comptroller Personnel Fellowships Information Services Diaries Oral Histories Counsel Secretary Minutes and Officers Actions Dockets Declinations (100F) Non-textual Materials Communications Office
Biographical / Historical
The China Medical Board was established in November, 1914 as a division of The Rockefeller Foundation for the purpose of developing modern medicine in China. Its program was based on the recommendations of the China Medical Commission which consisted of Harry Pratt Judson, Roger S. Greene and Francis W. Peabody. The group traveled to China, the Philippines and Japan in the spring of 1914 visiting medical schools, mission hospitals and colleges and universities. The plan which was adopted was to develop two medical schools, strengthen mission and other hospitals and provide scholarships for Chinese and foreign doctors and nurses.
Wallace Buttrick was Director from 1914-1918, while Roger Greene was the Resident Director in China. On Mr. Buttrick's retirement, George E. Vincent became Director. In 1922 Dr. Vincent became General Director while Mr. Green became Director and Henry S. Houghton assumed the position of Acting Resident Director. Mr. Green became General Director in 1925 and N. Gist Gee joined the staff in 1926 as advisor in premedical education.
Peking and Shanghai were chosen as sites of support because two relatively strong medical schools already existed there. In the autumn of 1951 Wallace Buttrick, William H. Welch, Simon Flexner and Frederick L. Gates traveled to China to develop a program for the Peking school. The Union Medical College of Peking was supported by several missionary boards, hence the word union. It was purchased by the China Medical Board in 1915 and chartered by the Regents of the State of New York in 1916. Franklin C. McLean was elected Head of the College. Trustees represented both The Rockefeller Foundation and the missionary boards. A construction program was started in 1916, premedical classes began in 1917 and the College opened in 1919. Buildings were dedicated in 1921.
The same type of program was assumed for the Harvard Medical School in Shanghai, and trustees were incorporated in 1917 under a charter of the University of the State of New York. However, building was delayed until the completion of the Peking complex. Because the war increased the difficulties of getting materials to China and because of exchange and price spiral, the Peking construction program was lengthened and costs became prohibitive. In [1917] plans for the Shanghai school were dropped.
The functions of the China Medical Board were transferred in 1927 to the Division of Medical Education of The Rockefeller Foundation and in November, 1928, the land and buildings of the Peking Union Medical College were transferred to the China Medical Board, Incorporated, an independent organization.
The Rockefeller Foundation:
The Rockefeller Foundation was established by act of the New York State Legislature approved by the Governor on May 14, 1913, "to promote the well-being of mankind throughout the world." Between 1913 and 1928 the China Medical Board, the International Health Board, and the Division of Medical Education functioned as divisions of the Foundation, concentrating on the administration of programs in public health and medical education. A Division of Studies was created in 1923 to handle projects outside the medical field. These early years were experimental as the new foundation studied the methods of philanthropy and explored its relationships with other Rockefeller boards.
Although the Rockefeller Foundation is the largest and best known philanthropy founded by the Rockefeller family, it was neither the first nor the last to be established. The Rockefeller Institute for Medical Research (1901), the General Education Board (1902), the Rockefeller Sanitary Commission for the Eradication of Hookworm Disease (1909), and the Bureau of Social Hygiene (1911) all existed earlier. When the Foundation was created, the Sanitary Commission was disbanded. After the establishment of the Foundation, the Laura Spelman Rockefeller Memorial (1918) and the International Education Board (1923) were created.
The Rockefeller boards and their programs were reconsidered and reorganized in 1927-1928 in order to avoid overlapping programs. The International Health Board of the Foundation was disbanded and an International Health Division was organized. The China Medical Board, Inc., was established as a separately incorporated institution, and the China Medical Board of the Foundation ceased to exist. The Division of Studies was dropped and the Division of Medical Education was phased out. The Laura Spelman Rockefeller Memorial was combined with the Foundation and the Spelman Fund of New York was chartered to continue activities of the LSRM that were not absorbed by the Foundation. The International Education Board was disbanded.
As a result of this reorganization, the Foundation adopted a program which included public health work (administered by the IHD), the advancement of knowledge in the medical and natural sciences (in part taken over from the IEB), the social sciences (formerly the field of the LSRM), and the humanities and arts (shared with the GEB). The Rockefeller Institute and the Bureau of Social Hygiene were not affected by the reorganization. The program adopted by the Foundation at this time remained basically the same for the next twenty years.
As its files accumulated, the Foundation maintained a card index recording the names of institutional and individual grantees and correspondents. A microfilm copy of this index is available at the Archive Center.
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC. Researchers interested in accessing digital media (floppy disks, CDs, DVDs, etc.) or audiovisual material (audio cassettes, VHS, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. To request an access surrogate be made, or if you are unsure if there is an access surrogate, please contact an archivist.
Medical care; Epidemiology; Missionaries -- China; Charities; Missionaries; Beijing (China); Agriculture -- China; Epidemics; China; Shanghai (China); Life sciences; Philanthropy, Charity and the Nonprofit Sector; Public health; Charitable uses, trusts, and foundations; Agriculture; Medical sciences; Philanthropy; Peking. Union Medical College
- An Eight Month Experiment, 1933; 1040 feet (film) 29 minutes (Box 1, Dvd DVD AV 115, Reel AV 115)
  Scope and Contents
  Three part film about the Peking Union Medical College and its efforts to improve the treatment and conditions for mentally ill patients. Features the Bureau of Public Welfare as well as Peking Union Medical College, with footage of clinics, patient activites, procedures, therapy etc. Includes some graphic imagery.
  Reel 1: PUMC and Bureau of Public Welfare establish a mental hospital. Drs. Wei and Wang. Bringing patient to hospital, handcuffing. Views of patients during recreation. Palace of Prince Na for more space. Getting new clothes. In the yard.
  Reel 2: Expanding quarters. Cleaning, delousing, further extension. Teaching clinics for medical and nursing students. Patients going home.
  Reel 3: Dr. I. C. Fang inspects Psychopathic Hospital. Occupational therapy. Men's and women's nursing offices, compounds. Excited and quiet men and women. Private patients. Laundry. Deteriorated patients.
  Chinese and English titles.
  Physical Characteristics
  gauge/medium: 16 mm film
  black and white
  sound: no
  File Plan
  F1; II 50.6 Fb 7, 8, 9
  Conditions Governing Access
  All inquires to view films on their orignial format require advanced notice of at least 24 hours, and may necessitate notice of up to one week. Individual items, including those not available in modern formats, may be restricted from scholarly access at the discretion of RAC.The film has been transferred to VHS tape.
  Access to the original film is restricted. DVD copies are available for scholarly access.
  Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
  The film has been transferred to VHS tape.
- Peking and Its Environs, 1920; 400 feet (film) 32 minutes; 3 reels, 1 videocassette, three copies of access DVDs (Dvd DVD AV 122, Dvd DVD AV 2.10, Reel AV 122)
  Produced by the Peking Union Medical College, the film shows the activites of the city and its people, historic sites, local natural features, and the campus of Peking Union Medical College.
  Reel 1: Views of harbor. Coal hill. North Gate of Forbidden City, moat. T'ien An Gate, Wu Gate. Railroad Station, Chien Mi Men. Fruit and nut stands, open air market. Hsi Chih Men. Street scenes. Funeral procession, paper effigies burned at grave, monks and musicians in procession, mourners in sackcloth supported by servants precede bier, mourners in carriages follow.
  Reel 2: South Gate, PUMC. Preclinical Sciences and Auditorium, Clinical bldgs., hospital units, power plants. West Gate. South Residence compound. Old Summer Palace Ruins - Theater, throne room, lake, painted gallery, tower views. Temple of 1000 Buddhas, Bronze Pagoda, Marble Boat. Temple scenes at Chinese New Year. Camel Train.
  Reel 3: Country scenes in Kuo Shih Yang. Village schools, donkey grinding bean meal, fishing nets. Temple at Tan Cheh Ssu. Arrival of pilgrims at temple. Valley of Ming tombs, statues of the Triumphal Way. Scenes at main tomb at Jung Lao. Conveying persimmons to market. Views in Nan K'ou, pass through which Gengis Khan entered China, fortified village. Great wall. Chow K'ou Tien - site of Peking Man discovery. Excavating main hill. Deep pit represents floor cave in which Sinanthropus was found. Classifying fossils - cave shows evidence of use of fire.
  F2; II 50.6 Fb 4, Fb 5, Fb 6
  All inquires to view films on their original format require advanced notice of at least 24 hours, and may necessitate notice of up to one week. Individual items, including those not available in modern formats, may be restricted from scholarly access at the discretion of RAC.
  The film has been transferred to VHS tape and DVD. DVD copies are available for scholarly access.
- Appropriations, 1913-1929; 1
  Arrangement note
  Series I, Appropriations, is divided into two subseries.
  China Medical Board Appropriations Index
  A card index to China Medical Board records, Series 1.1: Appropriations – Numerical, and Series 1.2: Appropriations – Alphabetical is available for use.
  Series 1.1 files are indicated by index numbers on the right edge of the index cards. For example, #64 = Church Missionary Society (London). The index cards are located in drawers 1-8 of the 72-drawer cabinet next to the RAC's reading room.
  Series 1.2 files are indicated by the file’s title (without an index number).
  The CMB Appropriations Index cards are located in drawers 5-8 of the 72-drawer cabinet next to the RAC's reading room.
  - Appropriations - Numerical, 1913-1918; 1
    Subseries 1 is in a numerical filing system. Each person, organization or topic has been given a number. In general the administrative topics run for the first 50 numbers. Numbers 50-83 are the missionary societies. From #84 on come the individual mission hospitals. They are filed according to province. Anhui runs from 84-88, Chekiang from 89-100 and so on.
    Numerous cross references exist in most of the files. They indicate a reference for the year only, rather than for a specific date.
    When consulting a folder on a particular missionary society or hospital, it is wise to also check the other society folders of society hospitals for additional material.
    Other Finding Aids
    A Society and Hospital Index is available in the print version of the finding aid.
    Appropriations - Numerical Index
    A card index to China Medical Board records, Series 1.1: Appropriations - Numerical is available for use. Series 1.1 files are indicated by index numbers on the right edge of the index cards. For example, #64 = Church Missionary Society (London). The CMB Appropriations - Numerical Index cards are located in drawers 1-4 of the 72-drawer cabinet next to the RAC's reading room.
    - 1. General Information 1913-18, 1913-1918 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      Scope and Contents note
      Correspondence, medicine and education in China, students, nurses, physicians, cooperation among existing groups.
    - 1. General Information 1913-18, 1913-1918 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - 1. General Information 1913-18, 1913-1918 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - 1. General Information 1913-18, 1913-1918 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - 1. General Information 1913-18, 1913-1918 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - 1. General Information 1913-18, 1913-1918 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - 1. General Information 1913-18, 1913-1918 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - 1. General Information 1913-18, 1913-1918 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - 2. China Medical Board 1914-16, 1914-1916 (Box 1, Folder 9)
      Tustees, Advisory Commitee, notices, plans, North China Language School.
    - 2. China Medical Board 1917-18, 1917-1918 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - 2.1 Charter and Bylaws, 1915-1916 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - 2.2 Executive Committee, 1916-1917 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - 2.3 Meetings, 1914-1918 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - 2.4 Dockets, 1914-1916 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - 2.5 Resident Director 1914-1918 (Box 2, Folder 15)
      Power of attorney, Harvard agreement, contagious diseases, political situation - union institutions, school requirements, staff, funds, Shanghai Medical School, nurses, fellowships, Worl War I, P. U. M. C. construction, Red Cross emergency relief.
    - 2.5 Resident Director 1914-1918 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - 2.5 Resident Director 1914-1918 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - 2.5 Resident Director 1914-1918 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - 2.5 Resident Director 1914-1918 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - 2.5 Resident Director 1914-1918 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - 2.5 Resident Director 1914-1918 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - 2.5 Resident Director - Reports (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - 2.6 Press and Publicity (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - 2.7 Committees to China and Reports, 1914-1917 (Box 3, Folder 24)
      China Medical Commission
    - 2.7 Committees to China and Reports, 1914-1917 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - 2.7 Committees to China and Reports, 1914-1917 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - 2.7 Committees to China and Reports, 1914-1917 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - 2.7 Committees to China and Reports, 1914-1917 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - 2.7 Committees to China and Reports, 1914-1917 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - 2.8 Appropriations and Appointments, 1915-1917 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - 2.9 Publications, 1917-1918 (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - 2.10 Committees, 1916-1918 (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - 2.11 Documents of Records (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - 3. Work of Missionaries, 1915-1918 (Box 4, Folder 34)
      Clippings, politics, bibliography, delegations to the U.S.
    - 4. Applications, 1913 - Jun-Jul 1916 (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - 4. Applications, 1913 - Jun-Jul 1916 (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - 4. Applications, 1913 - Jun-Jul 1916 (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - 4. Applications, 1913 - Jun-Jul 1916 (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - 4. Applications, 1913 - Jun-Jul 1916 (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - 4. Applications, 1913 - Jun-Jul 1916 (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - 4. Applications, Aug-Sep 1916-1918 (Box 5, Folder 41)
    - 4. Applications, Aug-Sep 1916-1918 (Box 5, Folder 42)
    - 4. Applications, Aug-Sep 1916-1918 (Box 5, Folder 43)
    - 4. Applications, Aug-Sep 1916-1918 (Box 5, Folder 44)
    - 4. Applications, Aug-Sep 1916-1918 (Box 5, Folder 45)
    - 4. Applications, Aug-Sep 1916-1918 (Box 5, Folder 46)
    - 5. Fellowships, 1914-1918 (Box 5, Folder 47)
    - 5.1 Tsing Liang Li, 1915-1917 (Box 5, Folder 48)
    - 5.2 T. M. Li, 1914-1916 (Box 5, Folder 49)
    - 5.4 S.J. Shen, 1914-1917 (Box 6, Folder 50)
    - 5.5 E. T. Tsen, 1915 (Box 6, Folder 51)
    - 5.6 Peter Kiang, 1914-1917 (Box 6, Folder 52)
    - 5.12 Lillian Wu, 1916-1918 (Box 6, Folder 53)
    - 5.13 Mildred Wu, 1915-1917 (Box 6, Folder 54)
    - 5.15 S. T. Chiu, 1915-1917 (Box 6, Folder 55)
    - 5.18 W. S. Thacker - Neville, 1916-1918 (Box 6, Folder 56)
    - 5.20 Elizabeth Sze, 1915-1918 (Box 6, Folder 57)
    - 5.21 F. C. Yen, 1914-1915 (Box 6, Folder 58)
    - 5.22 A. M. Dunlap, 1916-1918 (Box 6, Folder 59)
    - 5.23 Anna Vogt, 1916-1918 (Box 6, Folder 60)
    - 5.25 Walter Hiltner, 1917 (Box 6, Folder 61)
    - 5.27 C. C. Liau, 1917-1918 (Box 6, Folder 62)
    - 5.28 Grace Yoh, 1917-1918 (Box 6, Folder 63)
    - 5.29 E. Y. Kau, 1917-1918 (Box 6, Folder 64)
    - 5.31 W. W. Peter, 1916-1918 (Box 6, Folder 65)
    - 5.32 Mabel McCracken, 1917 (Box 6, Folder 66)
    - 5.33 Charles A. Hayes, 1917 (Box 6, Folder 67)
    - 5.34 Li Yuin Tsao, 1917-1918 (Box 6, Folder 68)
    - 5.35 Lan Sung Woo, 1917-1918 (Box 6, Folder 69)
    - 5.36 Charles Roys, 1917-1918 (Box 6, Folder 70)
    - 5.37 Grace Crandall, 1918 (Box 6, Folder 71)
    - 5.38 H. P. Chu, 1918 (Box 6, Folder 72)
    - 5.39 C.S. Mei, 1916-1918 (Box 6, Folder 73)
    - 5.40 Mary Tai, 1918 (Box 6, Folder 74)
    - 5.42 J. M. Wright, 1918 (Box 7, Folder 75)
    - 6. Pharmacy Scholarships, 1916 (Box 7, Folder 76)
    - 6.2 K. T. How and Hsiips, 1915-1918 (Box 7, Folder 77)
    - 7. Nursing Scholarships, 1914-1916 (Box 7, Folder 78)
    - 7.2 Chinese Nurses Studying in the U.S., 1917-1918 (Box 7, Folder 79)
    - 7.2 Chinese Nurses Studying in the U.S., 1917-1918 (Box 7, Folder 80)
    - 8. The Rockefeller Foundation, 1916-1917 (Box 7, Folder 81)
    - 8.1 Comptroller, 1915-1918 (Box 7, Folder 82)
      A-Z P. U. M. C. Building Arrangements
    - 8.1 Comptroller, 1915-1918 (Box 7, Folder 83)
    - 8.2 Treasurer, 1914-1916 (Box 7, Folder 84)
    - 9. Secondary Education, 1915-1918 (Box 7, Folder 85)
    - 10. Pre-Medical Education, 1916-1917 (Box 7, Folder 86)
    - 11. Medical Education, 1912-1918 (Box 7, Folder 87)
      Full-time teachers, cooperation with Chinese, medical education for women, anti-vivisection.
    - 11. Medical Education, 1912-1918 (Box 7, Folder 88)
    - 11. Medical Education, 1912-1918 (Box 7, Folder 89)
    - 12. Public Health, 1914-1918 (Box 8, Folder 90)
      Hankow Merchants Benevolent Association, Leung Tat Chui, plague, yellow fever, hookworm, TB, milk, leprosy, PH lectures, exhibits, conferences.
    - 12. Public Health, 1914-1918 (Box 8, Folder 91)
    - 12. Public Health - Clippings (Box 8, Folder 92)
    - 12. Public Health - Reports, Clippings, Pamphlets (Box 8, Folder 93)
    - 13. Hospitals, 1914-1917 (Box 8, Folder 94)
      Mission hospitals
    - 13. Hospitals - Reports (Box 8, Folder 95)
    - 13. Hospitals - Reports (Box 8, Folder 96)
    - 13. Hospitals - Reports (Box 8, Folder 97)
    - 13. Hospitals - Reports (Box 8, Folder 98)
    - 13.1 TB Hospitals, 1914-1917 (Box 9, Folder 99)
    - 13.2 Hospital Bureau of Standards and Supplies, 1916-1917 (Box 9, Folder 100)
    - 13.3 Hospital Administration, 1916-1917 (Box 9, Folder 101)
    - 13.4 Hospital Equipment, 1916-1917 (Box 9, Folder 102)
    - 14. Garden City Address, 1916 (Box 9, Folder 103)
      Wallace Buttrick
    - 15. Passports (Box 9, Folder 104)
    - 17. Commercial Cable Company, 1915-1918 (Box 9, Folder 105)
    - 18. China Continuation Committee of the National Missionary Conference - Shanghai, 1915-1918 (Box 9, Folder 106)
      Interdenominational. E. C. Logenstine, W. S. Lewis
    - 20. Roger S. Greene, 1915-1918 (Box 9, Folder 107)
      Political situation, organization, Wallace Buttrick in Japan.
    - 21. Jerome D. Greene, 1915-1918 (Box 9, Folder 108)
    - 22. Harry Pratt Judson, 1912-1918 (Box 9, Folder 109)
    - 23. John D. Rockefeller, Jr., 1914-1917 (Box 9, Folder 110)
    - 24. Wallace Buttrick, 1914-1918 (Box 9, Folder 111)
    - 24. Wallace Buttrick, 1914-1918 (Box 9, Folder 112)
    - 24. Wallace Buttrick, 1914-1918 (Box 9, Folder 113)
    - 25. Wickliffe Rose, 1914-1917 (Box 9, Folder 114)
    - 26. Simon Flexner, 1914-1918 (Box 9, Folder 115)
    - 27. Francis W. Peabody, 1914-1917 (Box 9, Folder 116)
    - 28. Frederick T. Gates, 1914-1917 (Box 9, Folder 117)
    - 29. John R. Mott, 1914-1917 (Box 10, Folder 118)
    - 30. Frank J. Goodnow, 1914-1918 (Box 10, Folder 119)
    - 31. Starr Murphy, 1917-1918 (Box 10, Folder 120)
    - 32. William H. Welch, 1914-1918 (Box 10, Folder 121)
    - 33. E. C. Sage, 1914-1917 (Box 10, Folder 122)
    - 34. Frederick L. Gates, 1915-1918 (Box 10, Folder 123)
    - 35. Paul S. Reinsch, 1915-1916 (Box 10, Folder 124)
    - 36. Forms (Box 10, Folder 125)
    - 37. C. Judson Herrick, 1915-1916 (Box 10, Folder 126)